[{"question_id": 0, "question": "Who is the main villain in KGF ?", "options": ["Garuda", "Rocky", "Adheera", "Sethupathi"], "answer": "a"}, {"question_id": 1, "question": "Who is the leader of the Night\u2019s Watch in GOT (early seasons) ?", "options": ["Jon Snow", "Jeor Mormont", "Tormund", "Benjen Stark"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 2, "question": "Who is known as the Mother of Dragons in GOT ?", "options": ["Cersei Lannister", "Daenerys Targaryen", "Sansa Stark", "Arya Stark"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 3, "question": "Who becomes the King in the North in GOT ?", "options": ["Robb Stark", "Jon Snow", "Ned Stark", "Bran Stark"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 4, "question": "What is the name of Jon Snow\u2019s direwolf ?", "options": ["Nymeria", "Ghost", "Grey Wind", "Summer"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 5, "question": "Who killed the Night King in GOT ?", "options": ["Jon Snow", "Arya Stark", "Bran Stark", "The Hound"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 6, "question": "What is Eleven\u2019s real name in Stranger Things ?", "options": ["Jane Hopper", "Jane Ives", "Millie Brown", "Sarah Hopper"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 7, "question": "Who is the police chief of Hawkins ?", "options": ["Mike Wheeler", "Jim Hopper", "Steve Harrington", "Bob Newby"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 8, "question": "What is the alternate dimension called in Stranger Things ?", "options": ["Dark World", "Upside Down", "Shadow Realm", "Other Side"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 9, "question": "Who is Dustin\u2019s pet Demogorgon ?", "options": ["Dart", "Spike", "Shadow", "Gorgon"], "answer": "a"}, {"question_id": 10, "question": "What is the name of the town in the series FROM ?", "options": ["Hawkins", "Rivertown", "Unknown Town", "Castle Rock"], "answer": "c"}, {"question_id": 11, "question": "What appears at night in the series FROM ?", "options": ["Ghosts", "Monsters", "Zombies", "Aliens"], "answer": "b"}, {"question_id": 12, "question": "Who is the sheriff in FROM ?", "options": ["Boyd Stevens", "Jim Matthews", "Victor", "Kenny Liu"], "answer": "a"}, {"question_id": 13, "question": "Who played Iron Man in Indian dubbing of Avengers ?", "options": ["Hrithik Roshan", "Shah Rukh Khan", "Rajinikanth", "Robert Downey Jr."], "answer": "d"}, {"question_id": 14, "question": "Which movie features the dialogue \u201cKitne aadmi the?\u201d ?", "options": ["Sholay", "DDLJ", "KGF", "Don"], "answer": "a"}, {"question_id": 15, "question": "Who is known as the King of Bollywood ?", "options": ["Salman Khan", "Aamir Khan", "Shah Rukh Khan", "Akshay Kumar"], "answer": "c"}, {"question_id": 16, "question": "Which Indian movie is about two engineers and friendship ?", "options": ["3 Idiots", "PK", "Dangal", "Chak De India"], "answer": "a"}, {"question_id": 17, "question": "Who is the father of Ned Stark ?", "options": ["John Snow", "Robert Baratheon", "Rickard Stark", "Benjen Stark"], "answer": "c"}]